Contact

punayjimpaul@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jim-paul-punay-514ba9177 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Qualtrics Quality Control Databases

Certifications

Google Data Analytics
IBM Data Analyst
Lean Six Sigma Green Belt

Jim Paul Punay

Data Analyst, Operational Research & Reporting | Six Sigma Green Belt & Continuous Improvement Professional Philippines

Summary

A responsible, approachable and confident person, highly self motivated, who works hard to achieve the best in every situation. Versatile individual with experience in collecting, transforming, and organizing data for analysis to help make informed decision. Proficient of platforms for effective data analysis, including SQL, spreadsheets, Tableau, R and Python. Previously working with programming languages of C++ and Java. Strong communication, organizational, and analytical skills is my expertise and finds reward in gaining responsibility, goals and objectives. A six sigma green belt holder.

Experience

Qualfon

Data Analyst, Operational Research & Reporting June 2023 - Present (1 year 3 months)

Cebu, Central Visayas, Philippines

- Generated reports by gathering data and presenting it in a manner that is intuitive and professional
- Used reporting tools to monitor key performance metrics regarding website and customer behavior, as well as backend/front end errors
- Conducted research on issues encountered by customers and gather findings to produce comprehensive and insightful results
- Effectively communicated research findings in a clear and concise manner that is easily understood by business units, IT, and executives alike
- Provided full support during production releases, with the willingness to provide before/after hours support when needed
- Properly documented issues and findings regarding all aspects of the job
- Trained and mentor junior members of the team to ensure quality and efficiency of work performance is minimally affected
- Used work collaboration tools to effectively manage tasks and assign items accordingly

With Intelligence

Data Research Analyst

June 2022 - June 2023 (1 year 1 month)

- ·Took ownership of a global universe of investors
- ·Tracked and Monitored Financial Markets
- ·Updated Key Financial Data
- ·Ensured all financial data are accurate and up to date
- ·Maintained a high level of quality across all profile builds
- ·Liaised with contacts primarily through outbound emails and phone calls (internationally)

Freelance

Software Developer

June 2020 - April 2022 (1 year 11 months)

- designed and coded software for businesses and consumers
- Gathered and evaluated user feedback
- Created technical documentation for reference and reporting
- Recommended and executed improvements
- Integrated software components and third-party programs
- Verified and deployed programs and systems
- Troubleshoot, debugged and upgraded existing software

Accenture

Business Associate

October 2019 - May 2020 (8 months)

-responsible for helping in identifying inefficiencies in operations and developing solutions

Education

University of Cebu

Computer Software Servicing · (2017 - 2019)

Saint Paul College Foundation Inc.

High School · (June 2014 - 2017)